stylepantry.com 2018-12-22

# Style Pantry | Privacy Policy

## Our Commitment to Your Privacy

This site is owned and operated by Style Pantry, LLC. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At Style Pantry, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.

Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.

### The Information We Collect:

When you participate in activities on Style Pantry’s website, you provide certain personally identifiable information (PII). Examples of this information may be any of the following: your name, e-mail address, organization affiliation, personal address, personal phone number, personal demographic information, and/or contact preferences.

### The Way We Use Information:

We review the site traffic information to learn which area of the site is helpful for our customers and which are not. This helps us make improvements to the site.

### Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Our site uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to encrypt any passwords and credit card information that you enter. SSL secures your data while it travels from your computer to ours.

### Online Newsletters

When you subscribe to our online newsletters, there are instructions at the bottom of your e-mail newsletter telling you how to unsubscribe if you ever wish to do so.

### Surveys

Style Pantry may occasionally conduct user surveys to better target our content to our audience. We never share any of this information about specific individuals with any third party.

### Children

Consistent with the Federal Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we will never knowingly request personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 13 without requesting parental consent. Kids, please, be sure to ask your parents for permission before you send any information about yourself to us or anyone else online or over the Internet.

### Cookies

We use cookies on our website to help you in your online surfing and to help tailor your experience at our website. Cookies are little bits of electronic information that a website can store on your computer to help make surfing online easier and to help personalize your visit to Style Pantry website. The cookie itself does not contain personal information, although it will enable us to relate your use of this site to information that you have specifically and knowingly provided. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can’t read data off your hard drive or read cookie files created by other sites. Style Pantry uses cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above). Our advertising system delivers a one-time cookie to better track ad impressions and click rates.

You can refuse cookies by turning them off in your browser. If you’ve set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies, you will receive the warning message with each cookie. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use this site. However, you may be unable to shop online or participate actively in message boards, forums, polling, and surveys.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on your prior visits to this website.  Google’s use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.  _Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting  [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/). (Alternatively, you can learn how to opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)_

### Sharing of the Information

Style Pantry uses the above-described information to tailor our content to suit your needs and to better understand our audience’s demographics. We will not share information about individual users with any third party, except to comply with applicable law: (1) to comply with any applicable laws or to respond to a court order, subpoena, search warrant, or other legal process received by Style Pantry; (2) to protect the safety of members of the public or users of Style Pantry’s website; or (3) to enforce our Terms of Use or to protect our rights or property. Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, Style Pantry will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary.

### Your Consent

By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by Style Pantry. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
